This particular piece is important.
I think it's been used a lot here.
We use it a lot.
I use it in classes, in coursework,
when we're trying to think about things around policing
specifically.
But it's especially important to me too,
because the first place I used was in Durham.
It was the kind of the take back the community pushing back
against the policing initiatives that
were being led around that, the night out for safety and democracy,
and Durham's close to home here.
So we kind of, to me, it's always been in some ways connected
to where we are in an interesting way and thinking about it.
But it's hanging in my office.
I want my students to see it when they come in
that what safety looks like is, in fact, not police, but this.
So I just walk us through this one.
Well, this was the first image I made that blew up before Marsha.
And it was a commission from Ella Baker Center.
And the reason it blew up, and this taught me about timing,
because it just happened to be released,
when the verdict was coming down around Trayvon's murder
and the national outrage about that and grief.
And I think the very powerful words that actually, I think it was in a meeting
with me and Zach and Emeraldis.
I think Emeraldis De Hussu's molestine might have come up with these words.
And now I'm like, I wish I had credited her.
I mean, used with permission, but I feel very aware
of wanting to be abundance in my crediting.
So us too.
Yes, yes.
And what it meant to show a black young man in a hoodie at that moment.
Okay.
So the text says, I don't watch my neighbors.
I see them.
We make our community safer together against a blue starry sky
with a drawing, implying apartment building.
And you see Asian elder grandma in the middle ground leaning on her window sill.
And a porch stoop with a brown skin woman, a hijab reading a book to her child.
And in the foreground is a young black young man on, you know, scraper bike wearing a hoodie.
This was earlier than the Marcha poster.
So I think I was still I worked as a designer primarily for 10 years.
So this was sort of before I started doing hand lettering.
And I think this poster is more simple.
And some ways than some of my other images.